export const numbersData = [
  { question: "一", reading: "いち", correctAnswer: 1 },
  { question: "二", reading: "に", correctAnswer: 2 },
  { question: "三", reading: "さん", correctAnswer: 3 },
  { question: "四", reading: "よん", correctAnswer: 4 },
  { question: "五", reading: "ご", correctAnswer: 5 },
  { question: "六", reading: "ろく", correctAnswer: 6 },
  { question: "七", reading: "なな", correctAnswer: 7 },
  { question: "八", reading: "はち", correctAnswer: 8 },
  { question: "九", reading: "きゅう", correctAnswer: 9 },
  { question: "十", reading: "じゅう", correctAnswer: 10 },
  { question: "十一", reading: "じゅういち", correctAnswer: 11 },
  { question: "十二", reading: "じゅうに", correctAnswer: 12 },
  { question: "十三", reading: "じゅうさん", correctAnswer: 13 },
  { question: "十四", reading: "じゅうよん", correctAnswer: 14 },
  { question: "十五", reading: "じゅうご", correctAnswer: 15 },
  { question: "十六", reading: "じゅうろく", correctAnswer: 16 },
  { question: "十七", reading: "じゅうなな", correctAnswer: 17 },
  { question: "十八", reading: "じゅうはち", correctAnswer: 18 },
  { question: "十九", reading: "じゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 19 },
  { question: "二十", reading: "にじゅう", correctAnswer: 20 },
  { question: "二十一", reading: "にじゅういち", correctAnswer: 21 },
  { question: "二十二", reading: "にじゅうに", correctAnswer: 22 },
  { question: "二十三", reading: "にじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 23 },
  { question: "二十四", reading: "にじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 24 },
  { question: "二十五", reading: "にじゅうご", correctAnswer: 25 },
  { question: "二十六", reading: "にじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 26 },
  { question: "二十七", reading: "にじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 27 },
  { question: "二十八", reading: "にじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 28 },
  { question: "二十九", reading: "にじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 29 },
  { question: "三十", reading: "さんじゅう", correctAnswer: 30 },
  { question: "三十一", reading: "さんじゅういち", correctAnswer: 31 },
  { question: "三十二", reading: "さんじゅうに", correctAnswer: 32 },
  { question: "三十三", reading: "さんじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 33 },
  { question: "三十四", reading: "さんじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 34 },
  { question: "三十五", reading: "さんじゅうご", correctAnswer: 35 },
  { question: "三十六", reading: "さんじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 36 },
  { question: "三十七", reading: "さんじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 37 },
  { question: "三十八", reading: "さんじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 38 },
  { question: "三十九", reading: "さんじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 39 },
  { question: "四十", reading: "よんじゅう", correctAnswer: 40 },
  { question: "四十一", reading: "よんじゅういち", correctAnswer: 41 },
  { question: "四十二", reading: "よんじゅうに", correctAnswer: 42 },
  { question: "四十三", reading: "よんじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 43 },
  { question: "四十四", reading: "よんじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 44 },
  { question: "四十五", reading: "よんじゅうご", correctAnswer: 45 },
  { question: "四十六", reading: "よんじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 46 },
  { question: "四十七", reading: "よんじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 47 },
  { question: "四十八", reading: "よんじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 48 },
  { question: "四十九", reading: "よんじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 49 },
  { question: "五十", reading: "ごじゅう", correctAnswer: 50 },
  { question: "五十一", reading: "ごじゅういち", correctAnswer: 51 },
  { question: "五十二", reading: "ごじゅうに", correctAnswer: 52 },
  { question: "五十三", reading: "ごじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 53 },
  { question: "五十四", reading: "ごじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 54 },
  { question: "五十五", reading: "ごじゅうご", correctAnswer: 55 },
  { question: "五十六", reading: "ごじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 56 },
  { question: "五十七", reading: "ごじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 57 },
  { question: "五十八", reading: "ごじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 58 },
  { question: "五十九", reading: "ごじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 59 },
  { question: "六十", reading: "ろくじゅう", correctAnswer: 60 },
  { question: "六十一", reading: "ろくじゅういち", correctAnswer: 61 },
  { question: "六十二", reading: "ろくじゅうに", correctAnswer: 62 },
  { question: "六十三", reading: "ろくじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 63 },
  { question: "六十四", reading: "ろくじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 64 },
  { question: "六十五", reading: "ろくじゅうご", correctAnswer: 65 },
  { question: "六십六", reading: "ろくじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 66 },
  { question: "六十七", reading: "ろくじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 67 },
  { question: "六十八", reading: "ろくじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 68 },
  { question: "六十九", reading: "ろくじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 69 },
  { question: "七十", reading: "ななじゅう", correctAnswer: 70 },
  { question: "七十一", reading: "ななじゅういち", correctAnswer: 71 },
  { question: "七十二", reading: "ななじゅうに", correctAnswer: 72 },
  { question: "七十三", reading: "ななじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 73 },
  { question: "七十四", reading: "ななじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 74 },
  { question: "七十五", reading: "ななじゅうご", correctAnswer: 75 },
  { question: "七十六", reading: "ななじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 76 },
  { question: "七十七", reading: "ななじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 77 },
  { question: "七十八", reading: "ななじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 78 },
  { question: "七十九", reading: "ななじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 79 },
  { question: "八十", reading: "はちじゅう", correctAnswer: 80 },
  { question: "八十一", reading: "はちじゅういち", correctAnswer: 81 },
  { question: "八十二", reading: "はちじゅうに", correctAnswer: 82 },
  { question: "八十三", reading: "はちじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 83 },
  { question: "八十四", reading: "はちじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 84 },
  { question: "八十五", reading: "はちじゅうご", correctAnswer: 85 },
  { question: "八十六", reading: "はちじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 86 },
  { question: "八十七", reading: "はちじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 87 },
  { question: "八十八", reading: "はちじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 88 },
  { question: "八十九", reading: "はちじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 89 },
  { question: "九十", reading: "きゅうじゅう", correctAnswer: 90 },
  { question: "九十一", reading: "きゅうじゅういち", correctAnswer: 91 },
  { question: "九十二", reading: "きゅうじゅうに", correctAnswer: 92 },
  { question: "九十三", reading: "きゅうじゅうさん", correctAnswer: 93 },
  { question: "九十四", reading: "きゅうじゅうよん", correctAnswer: 94 },
  { question: "九十五", reading: "きゅうじゅうご", correctAnswer: 95 },
  { question: "九十六", reading: "きゅうじゅうろく", correctAnswer: 96 },
  { question: "九十七", reading: "きゅうじゅうなな", correctAnswer: 97 },
  { question: "九十八", reading: "きゅうじゅうはち", correctAnswer: 98 },
  { question: "九十九", reading: "きゅうじゅうきゅう", correctAnswer: 99 },
  { question: "百", reading: "ひゃく", correctAnswer: 100 }
];
